<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Jay Morelli</title><link>https://www.jaymorelli.me/</link><description>Recent content on Jay Morelli</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:56:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.jaymorelli.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Git Worktree</title><link>https://www.jaymorelli.me/blog/git-worktree/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 09:56:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jaymorelli.me/blog/git-worktree/</guid><description>The most underrated git feature</description></item><item><title/><link>https://www.jaymorelli.me/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jaymorelli.me/cv/</guid><description>Colt Technology Services May 2022 - June 2023 My time at Atos was over, I felt I needed to go to a bigger project and the salary didn&amp;rsquo;t meet my expectations. I got an job offer from Team IT, a Portuguese consultancy, to work as a contractor in Colt Technology Services at the SD-WAN project.
I find the world of networking very interesting and intimidating, which made me excited to work with SD-WAN even tough I knew that there were networking engineers who would deal with all the network was nice to be around that environment.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://www.jaymorelli.me/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jaymorelli.me/about/</guid><description>Hi, welcome to my corner on the internet!
This site is a place for me to keep my own writting, a place for me to be a citizen of the web. Jammie Tanna and his article Why I Have a Website and You Should Too , was a big inspiration and really resonated with me.
I hope you can learn something from me as I have learned from many of the citizens of the web.</description></item><item><title>Now</title><link>https://www.jaymorelli.me/now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jaymorelli.me/now/</guid><description>This page is inspired by Derek Sivers&amp;rsquo;s post The /now page movement and the Now Movement . The purpose of this page is to share my interests and what I&amp;rsquo;m currently focused on.
What am I up to right now? Engaged, preparing for our wedding in 2025 Currently working at Siemens in the Industrial Edge . Actively blogging about technical and personal topics Looking forward to surfing more often Learning Kubernetes internals Web socket Reading Sapiens: A Brief History of Humankind by Yuval Noah Harari The Unicorn Project: A Novel about Developers, Digital Disruption, and Thriving in the Age of Data by Gene Kim Learning Go, 2nd Edition by Jon Bodner: Waiting for the public release as my O&amp;rsquo;Reilly subscription is finished Listening The Go Time Cup o&amp;rsquo; Go Fun fact: Shay created a minimalist version of the coffee mug after my request Grafana&amp;rsquo;s Big Tent Lex Fridman Podcast Ardan Labs Podcast Ponto Dev Podcast Backend Banter What are my interests?</description></item><item><title>Uses</title><link>https://www.jaymorelli.me/uses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.jaymorelli.me/uses/</guid><description>This page is a curated list of the tools that empower me as a software developer. Discovering pages like this has been a game-changer for me, providing valuable insights into optimizing workflows and uncovering hidden gems in the tech toolbox.
Pages like this is a goldmine for discovering new tools that elevate productivity and enhance the developer experience.
If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in exploring similar pages from fellow enthusiasts, be sure to check out the collection in the awesome-uses repository .</description></item></channel></rss>